Please do a live stream of your performance. This is... The opponent is a strong opponent. The opponent is a strong opponent. The opponent is a strong opponent.
The opponent is a strong opponent.
The opponent is a strong opponent. The opponent is a strong opponent. I'll do it. I'll do it.
I'll start the clock again. I'll start the clock again.
Here we go.
5 seconds.
4, 3.
Well, this week,
we've received many letters from many people.
Everyone, congratulations on your 17th birthday, Subie.
There are many wonderful letters.
By the way, do you actually have a birthday party?
I always do it, but my cousin's sister's birthday is the same.
Oh, I see.
And my cousin's other sister is also close, so we usually have a birthday party with all the relatives.
This year, we won't meet for 25 days, so we'll have a different day, so I haven't eaten a cake yet.
Oh, so you're going to eat it. Yes and I will eat on another day, so I haven't eaten a cake yet. Oh, so you eat it.
Yes, I eat it.
Is there anything you can imagine?
An ideal birthday cake.
I like chocolate.
Chocolate relationship.
But there are three of us, so I want two big cakes. If possible, I want three.
One cake per person.
That way, everyone can eat.
Choco is good.
Thank you. I haven't celebrated my birthday for decades.
Do you celebrate it at home?
Yes, at home.
I get a cake.
I eat it.
That's great.
It's been a while.
Really?
I wish I could do it.
I think it's been 45 years.
What?
It might be longer.
I see.
Everyone is working.
They are.
Well, that's it.
Then,
this week's closing segment is...
That one, right?
Oh, that one.
Imagining living things!
We did it!
Oh no.
So, we've received...
Here we go.
From Tokyo, Louis Bosti.
Thank you.
He's 17 years old, but he often gets messages from you.
Same year.
17 years old, that's a long time ago.
That's right.
That's nice. Are they're having a group reunion or something.
What do you mean? Why would that happen?
I mean, they're all going somewhere.
Yeah, they're on summer vacation.
But when they're 17, will they really start dating?
I think so.
They're not in a class. Do you really date people? I think so.
Like in class?
I wonder what Louis Vuitton is like.
I wonder if you're watching.
If you do, I'll send you her name and photos.
No way.
I can't announce it.
We can't.
Please do.
Here's the name of the person.
It's... Sadogashima Sado Island in Niigata.
The dialect there.
The dialect?
Can I read it?
Tonchibo
Tonchibo?
Tonchibo in dialect.
Yes. But, I wonder if the dialect is that strong that the words change so much.
I wonder.
One thing I can say is that it means that it is in Sadogashima.
That's right.
What?
I want to go to Sadogashima.
Hitose's brush.
It seems that Sadogashima is a very good place.
Is that so?
In the old days, it was famous for Kinzan.
In the Edo period.
It seems that Kinza was taken a lot.
It seems that it was amazing.
It seems that it was crispy.
That much?
The grandmother of this Louis Bosty is from Sadokashima.
And the dialect.
What is this?
Tonchibo.
What's wrong? Are you okay?
What is this?
I really don't know the dialect.
That's right. I don't know the dialect. I don't know either.
Is there any Hokkaido-specific one?
Like, you didn't pass the test.
I'm curious.
Hokkaido is close to the language. The intonation is close too. The words are similar, right?
Yes, they are.
The intonation too.
What? Isn't it a bit random?
It's the same.
How did you do it?
I see.
Indeed.
Isn't it good?
It might be terrible. It's terrible.
Hokkaido people say namara, namara.
Namara.
Namara is amazing, right, Miyuki?
Like a butterfly.
Namara is delicious.
Namara is cool.
I've heard of it.
I only know waya.
Waya.
So, first, Sensei
Tonchibo
Tonchibo, here it is
Oh, I see
You're good today
I'm good today, right?
Yes
You know what this is, right?
I know
Can I answer this?
Fua
That's right
I see
It's Japanese, so it doesn't change much
But it's like ton, chibo, and chi
That's true
Tonbo is a bit tasteless
It's like ton, chibo, ton, desu, sa
That's the image
Ton, chibo, ton, desu, sa
That's the image You always a bird. That's my image. You always draw flying things from above.
That's true.
Where do you draw from?
It's not decided from where, but from above.
But insects are usually stuck in samples.
So there's no reason to draw from above but you can draw birds from the top.
What?
You can draw birds from the top?
From the top?
Yes, from the top.
I'll draw a bird.
For example.
That's terrible.
Oh, I see.
Yes, that's right.
I see. I see.
Oh.
This is the first time I've actually drawn it in real life.
It's the first time you've shown it.
I see.
I draw birds like this.
What's the difference between this and this?
It's like you're looking for a mistake.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, that's it.
What about you, Sumie?
I should have draw like that.
Oh!
No, it's the same.
It's the same.
I was wondering how to draw it.
No, no, no.
Like a tonbo. No, no, no. It's like a chocolate banana.
You're too much into summer.
This is the mark of a tele-tone.
There's one, right?
It's a 7.
This is the right answer.
How is it? It's thick.
It's like a butterfly. It's like a butterfly. It's close to a bee. It's a tonbo. It's like a butterfly.
It's like a butterfly.
It's a dragonfly.
It's like a dragonfly.
Thank you.
You're so kind.
So, the correct answer is...
Ten!
Eh?
You know what it is, right?
It's a bit like Itachi.
It's about Ten.
Tonchibo?
Why?
I don't see it often.
I've never seen it in person.
There are various things like that. If you play a dialect, it seems that there is also a place called Tanuki in Tonchibo.
However, in Sadogashima, Tonchibo is called this TEN.
Only the face is white. Only the tip of the tail.
I've seen it once at the zoo, but it's a little mysterious.
It's just white on the face.
I'm curious.
It was a 10.
Well, well, well.
Thank you.
I want to show you again. Oh, I see.
This is wonderful.
This is also a picture of Subie from above.
That's right.
And her face is above.
Is it a picture from below?
That's right.
It's a face like this.
That's amazing.
It's a picture of Subie from below. I don't see the dragonfly from below. Wow, you drew it from the bottom.
I don't usually look at the dragonfly from the bottom.
I've never seen it.
I wonder what it feels like to draw a picture from above.
That's right. Well, well, we have a picture from the one who draw dragonfly from below.
Oh, I see.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's called a dragonfly artist.
A dragonfly artist.
There are three of them.
This one is the first one.
Yes, this one. This is it. The other day, I went on a family trip.
I went to the Oshino Hakkai in Yamanashi.
It's near Mt. Fuji.
There are many ponds.
I went there.
The weather was great.
This is a normal camera.
It's like oil painting painting. It's beautiful.
The sky is beautiful, and the feeling of the grass is really beautiful.
It's like it's flowing.
It was a little long.
The water was flowing quite vigorously, and it was cool just to look at it.
It was really beautiful.
It's a good place to rest.
There's a lot of spring water around there.
That's the water in Mt. Fuji.
It's really nice water.
I wanted to drink it.
The spring water in Mt. Fuji is so strong.
You can see it.
It's bubbling.
It's like sand is rolling.
I see.
There were a lot of people from floating. I see. There were many foreigners.
There were many.
And then,
Do you know this place?
This is a shop called
Houtou Fudo.
It's a shop called Houtou Fudo.
There are many shops in Houtou Fudo.
But this is the only one
with a white dome-shaped wall.
Why?
It's like a museum.
It's a museum in the east.
When you look at it from the outside, it's like a museum.
It's not air-conditioned.
There's a hole in the dome, and the wind is blowing through it.
I see.
So you can feel the wind without the air conditioner.
That's nice.
You can feel the nature.
This looks like it's in your eyes.
It looks like it's coming out of an EVA.
That's right.
The sky is blue, so it's like the sky is flying.
That's really good.
This is a
This is a photo of a lighthouse.
Wow!
I have to prepare it.
Yay!
It looks delicious!
There's a lot of food here.
The only thing we have is this.
There's only one.
So I came early and ordered it in less than 5 minutes.
There were 2 or 3 pumpkins in it.
Pumpkins are hot.
I know.
It was really hot and it was hard to eat.
But it was really delicious.
By the way, you're the type who couldn't eat hot food.
I don't think so.
But you're struggling so much.
By the way, I often order food from the kitchen.
It took me a long time to eat.
It's really hot.
It took me about an hour and a half.
It's quite a lot.
I brought only one of these.
There's a lid.
I put it on a lid and let it cool for a while.
So we let it cool for a while.
That's how hot it is.
It's cold in Yamanashi, right?
Originally, it was a military lunch box from the Sengoku period.
It was made on the battlefield, and eat it with everyone.
That's right!
As expected, you have a lot of bean knowledge.
I'm looking at small knowledge.
Isn't it amazing?
It's amazing.
The amount of knowledge is tremendous.
It's good.
It's good to be a good thing.
The taste was a little light here, it was spicy and it was really delicious.
I see. It's like, please put it in and eat it.
Ah, I know.
I know.
That's good.
It was delicious.
I love pumpkin.
It's delicious.
After all, a pumpkin is a must for a
knife. I love pumpkin. Pumpkin is a must for Houtou.
And there are a lot of mushrooms and vegetables.
It's a lot.
It's a good balance of nutrition.
It was delicious.
It was a great trip.
Yes.
Well, Did you about it. Yes. Well, then...
Did you have something today?
Yes.
Oh!
Oh, maybe...
What?
It's May 10th.
It's been a while.
It's January 10th. It's been a while. I'm January 24th.
You're a long way off.
Well, well, well. I'm sure he's here.
I think he's somewhere.
I've been given a lot of devil charges.
If you read what's written here...
What?
Me?
I'll read it.
It says, Subie-san.
When is Subie-san's birthday?
It's the 25th.
August.
So the closest is to Subie-san.
Yes.
Then! It's going to be like that. What? Then, Yes.
An old birthday present.
What?
Right?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Ah! It's huge!
What?
It's really huge!
A house?
I wish it was a house
What is it?
Oh, here it comes again
That face
Here it comes again
I think you guys don't know, so please check it out
I think you staff will understand, so please check it out. I think everyone will like it.
I love dogs.
Then I think it's better for the dog to be the MC.
That's what I said this week.
The staff just took the dog's stuff to the master.
And they took it right away. And it was taken so quickly.
So I thought it was this.
I thought it was a birthday present.
I was in a hurry.
A present.
This is probably a proper gift.
That's good.
Here you go.
Thank you.
It's close.
It's big.
Can I open it?
I want to open it.
I'll read the double charge.
Happy birthday to H&K's Subie at 17.
I'm looking forward to your birthday next week.
Thank you.
There's a story in the piano.
What? I'm going to Mas your birthday. Thank you. There's a song on the piano.
I'm going to say, I'm going to have a birthday.
Wait!
What is it?
What?
I can't see it at all.
Box?
This is...
Box? It's a box.
What?
This is...
Sports shoes!
Wow!
What?
This is really good!
This is a good one.
I can't see it.
It's cute.
Right?
Amazing.
I see. You like running shoes.
Yes, I recently got a pair of running shoes.
What? What?
What?
It looks good on you.
It's so cute.
It's so easy to wear.
What?
It's so strong.
It also has this.
What is this?
It's glasses.
It's true. It's a full-length. Oh, glasses! The sunlight is strong.
Sunglasses?
Matrix!
Is it a Matrix?
So cool!
It looks like it's going to be really fast.
It looks really fast's going to be really fast. It looks like it's going to be really fast.
Wow, that's amazing!
That's cool!
That's really cool!
That's really good.
I'm glad you ran as fast as you wanted.
Thank you very much.
And the sun is shining.
I'm sorry. Thank you very much. And the sun-dryer. Yes, it burns your eyes.
It's a good thing.
Please cut it again.
Thank you very much.
I will use it carefully.
Mr. Devilz, congratulations on your 17th birthday.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Tamamin, you have received a chocolate cake for your birthday.
Oh!
That's nice.
Kashihige-san, Happy birthday to you. I'll go to your live too.
Thank you.
Kahikahihosa-san, Happy birthday to you.
M-Nagaoka-san, Happy birthday to you.
I've never heard of that.
What about you, Subi?
And Mayu Yuinaoshi.
And Fubi Ryotaro.
Happy birthday.
Wow, thank you.
And Gashikashi.
Tan tan tan tan tanjoubi, Subie's birthday.
Thank you.
Tamamin, a gold medal in the There's no possibility of that happening. There's no possibility. Until it happens.
Really?
It's been 4 years, so 21 years.
That's right.
That's just right.
That's true.
It's just right for your physical strength.
That's right.
I'll consider it.
Thank you very much.
I used it carefully.
There's a harsh comment about Master's dog.
Master is annoying.
That's too much.
Thank you so much.
I can't see it.
Ah, please be careful.
It's a new monster. It might be a
I can't see it, so please be careful. It's a new kind of monster.
It might fight with the Kari-men Lier.
It will fight someday.
I'm happy.
You're saying that it will get faster.
It will get faster.
Recently, those sports shoes are really amazing.
Especially the ones that run long distances.
I think I'm getting faster.
The cushion and the front is a little bit like this.
It's a little bit like this. It's a little bit like this.
It's like you're moving forward.
That's amazing.
That's right.
By all means.
Thank you.
It's a loss.
That's good. If Mr. Sugie is going going to appear, I'll go to the site.
I'll go too.
Let's go to the site.
Let's go together.
That's right.
Sugie-san.
I'll go.
Nice.
I'll put on a shrimp-shaped hat.
Thank you.
So, the live start the live stream.
Master, we have to say that.
Oh, right.
That one.
The puzzle is...
Oh, cute.
I heard that it's starting to be delivered.
We want to deliver it, so we hope you'll finish it. And for the other project,
I think we'll deliver this white one as well.
If you can draw something on this and send it to us.
I see!
And if you can make it into an original puzzle.
That's great!
We'll see what you can do.
We'll do a show, like a master it. I want to see it. I want to see it.
I want to see it.
I want to see it. I want to do it anymore. That's right. I want you to send me a picture.
Thank you.
Hello, everyone.
Next week, at 8 p.m.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Thank you! you